Hi Viewers,
I am going to show you a demo on carpark web
application which I have hosted in Google
cloud compute engine.
url id is saravan-spring.com
This is a default login screen.
I have utilized Spring Security with csrf
token to provide high security.
I have provided csrf token security. It means
it is highly safety.
And any hackers cannot go into url directly
without validating the login screen.
I am going to show you some screens of Internal
and External Users and SignUp screen.
Any new user can sign up
for his new user account.
Tricky part is password encryption
and setting the User type.
I have intentionally typed some invalid values
to test hibernate validation will throw me error.
The error is thrown.
Email and Phone format is incorrect.
I have utilized Hibernate validations.
It is validating email format
and 8 digit phone no.
Hibernate validation. We don't have to write separate client side validation.
Ok. Now I am giving the correct values.
Let us see how it works.
As you can see the user type cannot be
modified by the external user.
By default, new user are assigned
to External user type.
Only admin can configure his user type.
I am going to show you how the user types
are dynamically listed.
List of User types will be dynamically generated
based on user login.
Admin user can see all the 3 user types.
Other users cannot change the user type
I am encrypting the password for data safety.
I am utilizing encryption algorithm available
in the spring framework.
Pls see the encryption part.
This is the password encryption algorithm.
I am using the BcryptpasswordEncoder.
Using that option I am encrypting the password
and store them in the database.
Also I would like to show you, how I have
done the spring security.
These are the available configurations for
spring security.
By default, it will always prompt you the
login screen.
And if it is successful, it goes to welcome
screen.
If there is a failure, it goes to error screen.
And username and password are captured from
the jsp page.
And it will be validated by the spring framework.
We don't have to do any single coding.
What I just need to do is I have to maintain
the user table.
I have to store the userName and password
in the user table.
So automatically spring framework will validate
and it will provide you the login status
on whether he is a valid user or not.
Also I am using the csrf token.
In parallel, I have to configure csrf token
in the jsp and so in ajax.
I am maintaining the
spring security configurations at the database
level rather than hardcoding in java file.
I am utilizing one of the table userRole.
For each and every role, I am setting the
access paths.
I have provided all the valid values and pressing
the Add button.
Once new user is created, then he can login
as an external user.
He can see welcome screen.
Now he can logout and relogin again.
He can see his details.
He can see menus related to external user.
If he wishes he can change his password.
Now that new user will login as a external
user, and he can see all the menus related
to external user.
Now Admin user
can login and he can convert his user type
from external to internal.
Now he can login and see his internal menus.
Menus are dynamically generated based on user
type.
Now he cannot go back to external menus.
Rather than creating two separate forms for
Add and Edit,
I am managing both within the same form.
I am applying saveOrUpdate method for both.
By doing this, I am eliminating code redundancy