Hello Viewers,
This is one of the POC web application,  which
I have developed for one of the Automative
corporate.
This is developed using Spring framework and
Kendo UI.
And in the backend,  I am using Glassfish web
server and Postgresql DB server.
This is a simple login screen.
Of course,  I am using Spring Security in this
web.
As you can see few sample user ids listed
here to login and test
At the bottom you can see an icon for Android
demo application which is .apk file which
you can download and install into your mobile
phone and browse as a
external user.
External user can reserve the carpark and
view his booking slots from his mobile.
Also I am going to show you the demo on how his
reservations are reflected into the POC web
application.